Come on. Now say it.
Teacher.
T-teacher.
I'm sure she just felt like it today, wanting me to call her that.
It's just role-playing to her.
I know.
I already know it.
Hey, what does it feel like?
It feels really good.
I can tell.
You know why?
It's because you really are.
You really are, teacher.
Damn it.
Damn it!
You will be ready.
my first time was just like in a dream I was in high school not too early not too late it was
with an older boy someone who everybody admired though of course it wasn't his first time he took
on the role of guiding me I just needed to play like everything was all new to me well not that
I needed to act since it really was my first time but the more I did act down the more he enjoyed it
and I would be loved all while enjoying my own worth and self-importance
something every girl wanted or even longed for and something all girls crave but can never truly have
but I could have it all and I wanted all of their jealousy I wanted to pile it all up
and line them all together then look and stomp on them all and use them on a whim
hmm I guess it's because that's all I know of myself
you know my adolescence wasn't like that
I'm pretty boring sometimes aren't I huh what no never oh I don't think I've ever been
self-deprecating in front of someone you couldn't hold a candle to you gross now it sounds like I was
whining I mean really self-centered but also like open-minded enough to make people think that
wait is this your plan see it's these sort of little surprises that really catch me off guard
I like it it's your appeal really that's what you like about me
uh so you're not mad at me why would I did you say something that should upset me
no silly little boy he thinks that I've accepted his reasoning
he's imagining that he's got me all figured out
so naive truly
uh Akane would you maybe like to go out next week anywhere whatever place you would like to go
damn kid
uh sorry I can't I'm going out with Mr. Kanai
I'll shatter your world
I'm being so kind really
I see then
even if you don't want to know you can't help it because we're so similar in this way
like how there's a part of me that can never change no matter what
or the timing that I choose to pull away
it's so sad
I wonder why do I keep repeating the same actions over again
because that's all I know
it's the only way
you see
that I know how to keep myself standing up
I must keep myself standing today
so that I can do it again tomorrow
I think I'm gonna lose it
that was the first time that Akane initiated it
god thinking about the meaning of a kiss
what is this j-pop
am I reduced to a girl
what he cheated on you again
just dump him already
yeah but I can't
I still really love him
and guys can do that sort of thing anyway
they don't need to be in love with the person or anything
so I'm sure he doesn't really love her
that's so naive
um but since I still love him
it still feels really good when we make love and I let him do things
too much information
way too much
why is that
why do feelings always take a back seat to the male sex drive
even I always thought that
we're terrible
oh what are you doing here
Mugi
I want to know
enlighten me
teacher
I can't
I'm going out with Mr. Kanai
please
don't go tomorrow
why not
I thought you were more understanding
was that my mistake
is it
because you're jealous of him
did you imagine what it was like
so how was it
god her attitude is so irritating
of course I didn't like it
and you know that
what do you expect me to say
you know what
I can't believe she hasn't been stabbed at some point
damn it
she could be so annoying
are you mad
you're so handsome
you look good mad
I
am
I am mad
so you are
do you hate me now
now I understand
I get it now
I figured it out
I know the reason
and why I'll never
be a match for her
turns out
I'm too scared
I don't want to be hated
by someone I love
please don't
don't go tomorrow
what if
I told you I hated you
what then
oh
I really like you
Mookie
that woman doesn't fall for anyone
she has no attachment to the affection she gets from all her suitors
she doesn't turn anyone away
but doesn't chase after those who decide to leave
that has to be
pretty lonely doesn't it
god
I love her so much
did I really think someone like her would ever fall for a kid like me
I'm so stupid
so stupid
and foolish
and utterly hopeless
uh
morning Miss Minigawa
hi
morning Mr. Kunai
although
I guess it's already past noon
oh
well I suppose you're right
now
I know that today is technically supposed to be Mr. Kunai's day but
do you like going to aquariums?
yes
uh
not really
but I thought
you might like them
so I thought I'd bring you
you didn't have to
we could have gone to wherever you wanted to
I'm sorry
we continued to go on dates since the bar
how many has it been now
I don't really remember the number
hey
today is Saturday isn't it?
yes
I believe it is
I want to see the penguins
sure
I don't understand
why haven't we gone back to a damn motel yet?
well
in all fairness
there have been guys like him
guys who obviously want to sleep with me
but don't ever make the first move
but this seems different somehow
you want to know something?
we've already slept together once haven't we?
and come to think of it
it basically felt like I instigated that time
what is this?
hold on
this is getting weird
weird reason number one
he slept with me once
but doesn't want it again
that's definitely too weird
why are penguins always so darn cute?
weird reason number two
this no sex thing is totally off-putting
yet we continue to go on our dates
as if everything is normal and dandy between us
that's too strange
and the worst
weird reason number three
and which clearly shows I hate this
he makes the situation look as if
I'm the one pursuing him
what is this?
this is irritating
I think I'm over it
I don't want him anymore
sorry
wannabe
thank goodness
I knew I must have left this thing in the classroom
uh
thanks
I had a really great time
time again
yeah
I had fun too
so
I'll walk you home
oh
that's not necessary
also
I was
Akane
huh?
whoa
another new guy
huh?
who's that
Takuya?
you really are such a hopeless slut
aren't you?
isn't that true
dear teacher?
ow!
and look who's calling the kettle black
you're just as big of a slut too
what the hell man?
how could you be so rude?
apologize to her this instant
stop it
I wonder why
it's none of your business anyway
I guess I was feeling extremely irritated that day
huh?
are you?
just shut up
huh?
you're the one who wasn't strong enough
to pass the test on being my boyfriend
you're so petty and jealous
you're nothing like a real man
why don't you recognize the reason
I didn't keep you around
and get over it already
just accept the fact that you were dumped
you asshole
that's what I wanted to say
but I can't
god
shut up
that's not part of my act
I'm not apologizing to anyone
hey
you there
uh
yes
that one's a real slut
that loves any man
she can climb up on
I'd be careful if I were you
see ya
hey
wait up
Miss Minigawa
look Mr. Kanai
what he said is true
I am
I'm a dirty slut
I'll basically sleep with anyone that looks my way
I'm not the pure innocent music teacher you think I am
I don't think I'll ever live up to your expectations of what a good woman can be
so if you please
let's just call this one our last date
see you later
wait
and by the way
I will answer all your questions even before you ask me
it's probably because I was born a slut
and yes
it's true that I feel good when different men give me attention
plus all the jealousy and heartbreak I can stir up in all of the other women
I think I honestly love that even more than what I can do to a man
I'm a bad person to get to know
there
that should do it
that should put him off me for good
you know what
I don't think I can stop any of it
well
it was very nice knowing you
alright
now it's finally over
I'll go home
watch some TV
and text another guy
maybe enjoy the company of a high school boy who is in love with me
it's time to go back to that life
the sooner the better
you
you don't have to stop
you can be exactly the way you are
so
so then just
hurry up and let go of me
what do you mean I don't have to stop
are you seriously saying that
I'm asking you a question
uh yes
sorry
I mean exactly what I told you
so you're a cheatable
what does that mean
maybe Mr. Kanai is more twisted than I thought
but he just seems so average
oh
so then
is
this our last date
it's not
wait
why did I just say that out loud to him
you know
to tell you the truth
I was surprised when you called me
oh
were you
it wasn't that he didn't let me go
I was the one who couldn't let go
how could that be
I'm the one who has always been able to let go of so many men over the years
hey
do you hate that I sleep with other men all the time
huh
what kind of an answer do I give for that
I
I don't much like it
of course you don't
but why not
uh
well
um
I guess jealousy basically
is that it
and jealousy comes from my need to go after you fully is mine
that makes sense
and what about you
you really don't feel
any of that
maybe I do
I guess I would get a little upset
if a guy I think would definitely fall for me
ends up falling for someone else instead
is she for real?
could it be?
though
that's never really
happened to me before
she's more childish than I thought
is she really this immature?
you'll never get the words you ever want to hear
from the person you want to hear from the most
that's just not how the world works
well
that's what I think
I also agree
I think so too
right
that's why we made the pact in the first place
instead
you could get the words anytime
from someone else who didn't care
well
well see there
it's superiority
always
maybe she's right
I love you
Luki
so much
I practically made her say it
on top of that
there's that awful part of myself
that used her as sentimental material
and the worst part of me
was intoxicated by it
it's the part of me
that just can't let go
of my superiority complex
so I can go on
and live an honest
respectable life
it's because
I'm too attached
to that part of myself
because I'm scared
and terrified
I'm afraid of changing anything
that lies within me
but
through it all
there was a person
who still loved me
despite all of this
so for that
I should change
I have to
if you really want to change someone
you first have to start
with changing yourself
yeah
you're right
I should have realized it sooner
you'll be just fine
it's better late than never
they say
well
I should be going
I get it
it's something I had to let go
in order to change
this familiar voice
and smell
you know
not even in my fantasies
could I ever let that part of me go
how long will I be relying on her
this is my last
attachment
you're awake
you sure do sleep a lot
maybe because you're young
come on now
I have to grade all of these papers
hey wow
seriously
Akane
I want to go on a date
there it is
this boundary
could we do this later
I'm not backing down
I'm done reading into all her different timings and signs
because
I'm just
yeah
I'm young
so what
even if I try to pretend
or act as an equal
I'm completely inexperienced
I'm indecisive
and I'm annoying to deal with
and it's
all because
I love you
god
I'm so lame
it's the worst day of my life
but
I've never felt this excited before
something's changing
where do you want to go
that's it
I'm still young
and hopelessly stupid
and easily excited
that's why
I still didn't realize
that this person gets caught up easily too
or so I thought
at least
I'll see you next time